Register of the Walter E. Shjeflo papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Printed matter, 1965-1985
  - Reports, 1967-1984
    - Refugee reports, 1967-1982
      Contains statements by Cambodian, Laotian, and Vietnamese refugees sent to families of American POW and MIA soldiers detailing sightings and possible last-known locations of said soldiers.
      - 1967-1976 (Box-folder 30: 13)
      - 1977 (Box-folder 31: 1)
      - 1978 (Box-folder 31: 2-3)
      - 1979 (Box-folder 31: 4-6, Box-folder 32: 1)
      - 1980-1982 (Box-folder 32: 2)
      - Undated (Box-folder 32: 3-4)
  - Serial issues, 1978-1985
    - American Legion, 1980 (Box-folder 32: 5)
    - Congressional Record, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 32: 6)
    - Military Law Reporter, 1983 (Box-folder 32: 7)
    - Forget-Me-Not Association Newsletter, 1982-1985 (Box-folder 32: 8)
    - National Human Rights Committee for POW-MIAs Newsletter, 1979-1983 (Box-folder 32: 9)
    - National League of Families Newsletter, 1978-1983 (Box-folder 33: 1-3)
    - Vietnam News, 1978 (Box-folder 33: 4)
  - Statements, 1979-1983 (Box-folder 33: 5)
    Contains statements and speeches by William P. Clark, Ann M. Griffiths, T.C. Pinckney, Eugene F. Tighe, and others.
- Photographs, undated (Box-folder 33: 6)
  Contains photographs of missing soldiers, military officials, and meetings between government and military officials.
- Bumper sticker, undated (Box-folder 33: 7)
  Contains one bumper sticker that says "Hanoi: Please Release Our POW-MIA."